&gt；&gt；steve kinney：所以如果我不多说一点就是疏忽了
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: So I would be
remiss if I didn't talk a little
关于服务工人的一点。
bit about Service Worker.
这是一个关于性能的研讨会。
This is a workshop on performance.
我不打算太深入地讨论服务工作者，因为我们今天已经讨论了很多内容
I'm not gonna go too deep into Service
Worker because we've covered a lot today
迈克·诺斯和
and Mike North and
我做了一个为期两天的关于服务工人的研讨会，我完全推荐你去看看。
I did a two day workshop on Service Worker
that I totally recommend you check out.
所以我有点喜欢服务工作者的高水平
So I'll kinda do like the high level
of what a Service Worker is and
如果你是这样的话那很酷。
if you're like that is cool.
猜猜有什么内容，你可以只在服务上观看10个小时
Guess what there's ten hours of content
you can watch exclusively on service
工人，我现在不会对它做那么多的公正，但是
worker, and I will not do nearly
as much justice to it now, but
我绝对建议你去看看。
I totally recommend that
you check that out.
它的名字叫“是不是进步的网络应用程序反应”是这门课程的名称。
It's called was it progressive web apps
in react was the name of the course.
&gt；&gt；[INAUDIBLE]
&gt;&gt; [INAUDIBLE]
&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：是的，进步网络
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Yeah, progressive web
应用程序是一种伞形术语，服务工作者是其中非常酷的一部分，
apps is kinda of the umbrella term that
Service Worker is a really cool part of,
这实际上就像，想象您可以构建具有以下功能的应用程序
that's effectively like,
imagine you can build apps that have
本机应用程序的超能力，但在您的浏览器中。
native apps' superpowers,
but in your browser.
它实际上是当今最酷的网络技术之一，
It's effectively one of the coolest
set of web technologies today,
我认为会改变很多事情
that I think is gonna
change a lot of things,
特别是现在Safari在新的Beta中支持它。
especially now that Safari
supports it in the new betas.
所以，当我们请求一个网页时，
So, effectively when we ask for a webpage,
我们刚刚谈过这个，浏览器进入网络，给我网页。
we kinda just talked about this, browser
goes to network, get me the webpage.
当你有一个服务工人，
When you have a service worker,
实际上，它像应用程序一样将自己安装到浏览器中。
effectively it installs itself
into the browser like an app.
你不是向互联网索取东西，而是向服务工作者询问。
Instead of asking the internet for
things, you ask the service worker.
这可以像我实际上使用Java脚本一样，
Which can be like I
actually with Java Script,
有目的地将一堆文件放在缓存中，并可以为您获取它们。
purposefully put a bunch of files away
In the cache and can get them fo you.
你可以写出一大堆逻辑。
And you can write a whole bunch of logic.
使用我们之前讨论过的标题，就像您设置的那样，
With the headers that we talked
about earlier like you set them,
如果他们有点像那些给浏览器的建议。
if they are kind of like those
suggestions to the browser.
你在标题中设置它们，你希望浏览器尊重一些。
You set them in the header and
you hope the browser respect some.
有了服务工作者，您可以编写JavaScript，您可以像这样，我想把
With service worker you can write
JavaScript you can be like, I want to put
你在缓存中，我想在我从缓存中取出东西之前检查一下，
you in the cache, I want to check this
before I pull something out of the cache,
你可以做一大堆非常有趣的事情。
and you can do a whole bunch
of really interesting things.
因此，因为您拥有该控件，所以您可以让应用程序离线工作。
And so because you have that control you
can have applications that work offline.
因为根据定义
Because by definition,
如果它可以脱机工作，这意味着您可以很好地控制网络
if it can work offline it means that
you can control the network pretty well
即使当你在线时也能获得令人难以置信的快速加载时间，对吗？
to get incredibly fast load times
even when you are online, right?
与之相对的是，设置响应头的位置就像是嘿，
Versus, like, setting that response
header where it's like hey,
也许不检查，你在控制，我不知道这是怎么回事。
maybe don't check, you're in control,
I don't know that's going on.
所以我们在缓存中有一些东西，在网络上有一些东西。
So we have some stuff in cache,
some stuff on the network.
每次提出网络请求都会进入服务工作，就像嘿，
Every time a network request is made
it goes to service work, it's like hey,
和缓存谈谈，对吧？
talk to the cache, right?
或者与缓存交谈，如果它不在缓存中，则与网络交谈。
Or talk to the cache, if it's not
in the cache talk to the network.
或者你真的可以做一些很酷的事情，比如和网络聊天
Or you can really do cool stuff,
like talk to the network and
获取新版本，然后将其放入缓存中。
get the fresh version, and
then put it in the cache.
如果它们离线了，去缓存并获取它，对吗？
And if they're offline,
go to the cache and get it, right?
它为您提供了对网络操作的大量编程控制。
It gives you a lot of programmatic
control over what you do with a network.
如果理论上可以，我现在正在研究的一个模式是
And if you can theoretically, one pattern
that I'm investigating right now is for
与那些具有唯一标识符的文件一起部署。
deploying with those files that
have the unique identifiers.
这意味着每当我部署新版本的应用程序时，
It means whenever I deploy
a new version of the app,
我正在销毁所有的缓存，每个人都必须再次下载所有东西，对吧。
I'm destroying all the caches and everyone
has to download everything again, right.
就像，太好了，我已经交付了客户价值和功能。
Like, great,
I've shipped customer value and features.
糟糕，我正在反复擦除缓存，对吗？
Bad, I am wiping out the cache repeatedly,
right?
也就是说，如果他们有这些假现金，我就部署一个新版本，
Which means If they had all these
false cash, I deploy a new version,
他们必须为再次获得他们付出代价，对吧。
they have to pay the cost of
getting them again, right.
这是生活的事实，没有真正的方法。
That's a fact of life,
there is no real way about that.
但在这种情况下，您可以对服务工作人员做的是提供服务
But what you could do with the service
worker in this case is have the service
工人，在他们下次访问时给他们旧版本。
worker, give them the old version
the very next time they visit.
给我看老版本，在背景中，嗯，他们没有注意。
Show me old version, in the background,
well, they're not paying attention.
下载新版本，替换缓存的版本，然后
Download the new version,
replace the cached one, and
下一次，无论发生什么，他们仍然可以获得瞬时加载时间。
next time they still get instantaneous
load times no matter what.
有一堆很酷的东西你可以和服务工作者一起做
There's a bunch of really cool stuff
that you can do with service worker
在时间的本质和事实上有十个小时的内容。
In the nature of time and the fact
there are ten hours of content on this.
我要在那上面下注一小会儿。
I going to punt on that one for
a little bit.
它在这里是因为我也像超级兴奋的进步网络应用程序和
It's in here because I'm also like
super excited progressive web app and
服务工作，我认为它真的很酷。
service work, and
I think it's really cool.